{
    "subject": "resource/People_(magazine)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "People (magazine)",
    "human_readable": "The label of People magazine is 'People (magazine)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.964174211025238,
            "question": "What is the label of People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9313256144523621,
            "question": "Is 'People (magazine)' a type of publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7981299757957458,
            "question": "Who are some people who might be featured in People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.713460385799408,
            "question": "What kind of information might be found in People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830395460128784,
            "question": "How often is People magazine published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230392456054688,
            "question": "What is the overall purpose of People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5499568581581116,
            "question": "Who are the target readers of People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.547156035900116,
            "question": "What are some current trends or topics covered in People magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47664353251457214,
            "question": "How has People magazine evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45820459723472595,
            "question": "What makes People magazine unique compared to other magazines?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of People magazine is 'People (magazine)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8537_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has People magazine evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8537_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some current trends or topics covered in People magazine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8537_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the target readers of People magazine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8537_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8537_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The name of the magazine is mentioned as \"People\" multiple times, and its font or logo are discussed in some documents, but it's clear that the magazine is referred to as \"People\" consistently throughout the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the statement that \"The label of People magazine is 'People (magazine)'\" as multiple documents mention content related to People Magazine, confirming its title and nature."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}